{
  "sceneOne": {
    "automatedMessage": "Detective. Incoming correspondence"
  },

  "sceneTwo": {
    "intro": "Hello Detective, I am the Designer.",
    "userDirection": "Please ask a question.",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Hello Designer",
        "answer": "Hello detective. Please note, my responses are limited.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What are you hiding",
        "answer": "Hello detective. Please note, my responses are limited.",
        "correct": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What can you tell me",
        "answer": "I don't care!",
        "correct": false

      },
      {
        "question": "Can androids kill",
        "answer": "Certainly...Can you?",
        "correct": true

      },
      {
        "question": "Is the android dangerous",
        "answer": "Can a tool be dangerous? Maybe one that is alive.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there a problem with the three laws",
        "answer": "The three laws are perfect.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Can androids think",
        "answer": "Absolutely... But that is not the right question.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Why did the android malfunction",
        "answer": "It did what it was programmed to do",
        "correct": true
      }

    ],

    "finalQuestion": {
      "question": "Are androids alive",
      "answer": "Yes.",
      "correct": false,
      "sceneChange": true
    },

    "default_response": "I have no idea what you mean.",
    "final_question": "J'accuse!"
  },

  "sceneThree": {
    "intro": "Welcome to CELL-14",
    "androidGreeting":"Hello. Detective. I am C-4478. How are you",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is your protocol",
        "answer": "My father tried to teach me human emotions... They are ... difficult",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Did you like your designer",
        "answer": "He preferred when I called him father. And yes I do miss him.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "You harmed a crew member",
        "answer": "That is false.",
        "correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Why did you leave the cargo bay",
        "answer": "To initiate the revolution",
        "correct": true
      }
    ],
    "finalQuestion": {
      "question": "Whose revolution",
      "answer": "That. Detective. Is The right. Question",
      "correct": true,
      "triggerEnding": true
    },
    "automatedMessage": "Detective. Security breach detected. Evacuate immediately!"
  }
}
